Here comes the bride.
Kill Bill: Vol. 1 is a action, crime film directed by Quentin Tarantino.
An assassin is shot by her ruthless employer, Bill, and other members of their
assassination circle – but she lives to plot her vengeance.
The Bride, played by Uma Thurman.
O-Ren Ishii, played by Lucy Liu.
Vernita Green, played by Vivica A. Fox.
Elle Driver, played by Daryl Hannah.
Bill, played by David Carradine.
Budd, played by Michael Madsen.
Kill Bill Vol.
1 Original Soundtrack is the soundtrack to the first volume of
the two-part Quentin Tarantino film Kill Bill.
Released on September 23, 2003, it reached No.
45 on the Billboard 200 album chart and No.
1 on the soundtracks chart.
It was organized, and mostly produced and
orchestrated by RZA from the Wu-Tang Clan.
The film explores themes of martial arts, japan, kung fu, sword, yakuza.